Oriana Thomson continues the fight in Academy City amidst the Daihaseisai.
（上条(かみじょう)）
大覇星(だいはせい)祭真っ最中の学園都市で―
逃走を続けるオリアナ＝トムソン
She managed to shake me and Stiyl off and shoot down Tsuchimikado as she escaped.
あとを追っていた俺とステイルは
出し抜かれ―
土御門(つちみかど)は狙い撃ちされてしまう
As if that weren't enough, she attacked Himegami, who just happened to pass by.
更に 偶然に居合わせただけの
姫神(ひめがみ)までも…
くそ… オリアナのヤツめ
絶対 許せねえ！
Damn it!
～♪
I'll never forgive her!
#12 Belvedere
Observatory
Damn it!
（上条）
ちくしょう
Tsuchimikado. I lost Oriana.
土御門 悪い　オリアナを見失った
（土御門）
どこに向かってそうとか
分かんねえかにゃ？
Can you tell where she's headed?
It looks like that route makes a large circle around the Seventh District,
ここのバスは第７学区を
ぐるりと回ってるらしいけど
but we have no way of knowing where she'll get off.
どこで降りるかは… 待てよ
Wait a minute.
（土御門）
何だ？　カミやん
What is it, Kami-yan?
What's Oriana doing moving around the city like this?
なあ　オリアナって
なんで街を歩いてるんだ？
（土御門）
はぁ？
そりゃ 俺たちが追撃してるから…
Well, we're chasing—
違う　その前だ
No, before that.
There was no Croce di Pietro deal in the first place, so she shouldn't be meeting anyone.
使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)の
取り引きがないってことは―
人と会うためじゃないよな？
It's dangerous for her to just wander around the city.
（上条）
なのに ウロウロと街を出歩くのは
リスクを高めるだけじゃないのか？
She must have her own reason for acting alone.
（土御門）
だとすると オリアナひとりで
動くべき理由があったってわけか
What reason could she have?
（上条）
理由って？
（土御門）
そこまでは分かんないにゃ
I don't know.
It may be that she's searching for some place which fits the conditions for using the Croce di Pietro.
使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)を使うための条件探しでも
してたのかもしんねえぜ
Conditions? Do you need to do something special to use it?
条件？　特別な環境じゃないと
使えないのか？
You should ask Stiyl about that.
（土御門）
その辺は ステイルに
当たってもらってたんだが
そういえば オルソラからの
メールを転送してきてたんだった
That's right, he forwarded me a text from Orsola.
そっちにも送るから
I'll send it to you now.
I read it, Kami-yan.
読んだぞ カミやん
This looks like a record concerning a cleaning of the Croce di Pietro's storage place.
こりゃ 使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)の保管庫の
大掃除に関する記録らしいにゃ
And? What did it say?
（上条）
…で 何て書いてあった？
使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)を保管するときには―
I seems they went to great lengths to ensure that the Croce di Pietro didn't come into contact with any light sources.
神経質なまでに
光を当てないように―
していたみたいだったにゃ
（上条）光？
Light sources?
They must have been taking precautions to keep it from activating.
きっと
不用意な発動を防いでいたんだろう
（上条）
…てことは
太陽を当てると発動するとか？
Maybe it activates upon contact with sunlight.
もし そうだったら
とっくにやってるはずだぜ
If that were the case, then she would have done that already.
Besides,
（土御門）
それに 大掃除は昼間のうちに
終わらせると書いてあるにゃ
this record mentions something about the importance of completing the cleaning before the sun goes down.
Time isn't a factor then...
じゃ 時間は関係ないのか
Right.
It seems they ran into some trouble with the workers, though.
ただ ここの保管員には
問題があったみたいだな
One of them was attempting to divine the stars.
勤務時間中に―
ホロスコープを使った星占いを
してたらしい
The stars?
星？
If the cleaning was so strictly carried out during the day, it must be something that's only present at night.
大掃除は昼間のうちにってことは
用心してたのは夜の光
So, starlight?
つまり 星のことなんじゃ…
That's true. By integrating star positions into a magic circle, one can increase its power tremendously.
確かに 星空に浮かんだ図形を
魔法陣に組み込むことで―
超巨大な力が得られるからにゃ
If the Croce di Pietro is some sort of antenna that's meant to pick up starlight,
（土御門）
使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)が 夜空の光を集める―
アンテナみたいな物だとしたら
I would guess that Oriana is searching for the best place to set it up.
オリアナが探しているのは―
アンテナを立てるために
最適な場所ってことになるにゃ
But Peter died on June 29th.
けど ペテロが死んだのは
６月29日なんだよ
On top of that, Japan has a completely different set of latitudes and longitudes compared to the Vatican.
更に 日本とバチカンじゃ
緯度も経度も違う
Unless she's found some way around those issues, the constellation theory is bust.
この問題をクリアできないと
星座利用説は成り立たないにゃ
Not that we have the time to think about such things any longer.
まあ
それを考えてる時間は もうない
とにかく動こうぜ
Let's make a move.
If we assume that she plans to use the constellations, our time limit is still...
星座を使うと仮定すると
タイムリミットは やっぱり…
Sunset.
日没か
じゃ 俺は どう動けばいい？
So what should I do?
Touma.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）当麻
（上条）うん？
What are you doing here?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
こんな所で何をしているの？
I-Index?
イ… インデックス？
Looks like Kanzaki Kaori didn't come here after all.
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）
結局 神裂火織(かんざき かおり)は来てないみたいね
ハァ…
Lidvia.
リドヴィア
I know what you want to say.
（ﾘﾄﾞｳﾞｨｱ）
言いたいことは分かっています
That girl you laid your hands on was just a commoner.
あなたが手をかけた少女は
ただの一般人でした
Her name is Himegami Aisa.
名前は姫神秋沙(あいさ)
非常に重要な力を有しているものの
Though she has a remarkable ability, she's not a magician in particular.
特に
魔術師というわけではありません
That Celtic cross is present purely to seal her powers, and has no offensive ability in itself.
あのケルト十字は
その力を封じるための霊装にすぎず
攻撃性も一切ありません
That's terrible...
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）
最低ね
It is quite terrible.
（ﾘﾄﾞｳﾞｨｱ）
まさしく最低です
This is the second time that we've harmed a commoner without any connection to our mission.
我々は 本件に関係のない一般人を
牙にかけました　それも２度
They are sinners who are lost, mistaken, and require our salvation and protection.
彼女たちは 我々が守るべき―
迷い 誤り 救いを求める罪人(つみびと)です
We can't afford to make any more mistakes.
我々は
もう二度と誤ってはいけません
For her sake as well, we must use the Croce di Pietro and take control of Academy City.
彼女のためにも 使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)を使用し
学園都市を
支配しなくてはならないのです
We'll really succeed at this, right?
ホントに 何もかも
うまくいくんでしょうね？
In taking Academy City, everybody's problems will be fixed, right?
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）
学園都市を手中に収めることで
皆が抱えている問題の全てが…
Touma, why aren't you with the rest of the class?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻　なんで
クラスのみんなと一緒にいないの？
You haven't participated in any afternoon competitions. Why?
午後に入ってから 競技に
参加してないよね？　なんで？
あ… ああ
運営委員のほうを手伝ってたんだ
I was helping out the Administration Committee.
おかしいな　クラスの連中には
メールを送ってたんだけど
That's odd, I thought I sent everyone a text about it.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）メール？
（上条）圏外だったのかな
A text?
Maybe I was outside the service area. The signal might not have reached a tower...
それとも センターまで
電波が届いてなかったのか？
（上条）
と… とにかくインデックスは
先に みんなのとこに行っててくれ
Anyway, Index, go ahead and tell everyone that.
Hey, Touma, they said that group gymnastics is next.
当麻 当麻
次は組み体操だって言ってたよ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ちゃんと来れる？
（上条）行くよ
You're coming, right?
I'll be there as soon as I can. I need to finish helping out first.
できるだけ早く手伝い終わらせてさ
I'll definitely go. Can you wait for me, Index?
ちゃんと行く
だから 待っててくれるか？
インデックス
Yep!
Sorry, Kami-yan.
（土御門）
悪いな カミやん
Let's get this over with.
こんな手伝い
早く終わらせちまおうぜ
But with this many people...
（上条）
とはいえ これだけ人が多いと…
"Wait up!" says MISAKA says MISAKA giving chase.
（ﾗｽﾄｵｰﾀﾞｰ）
待ってよって
ミサカはミサカは追いかけてみたり
（ﾗｽﾄｵｰﾀﾞｰ）
いいじゃんって―
"Come on, MISAKA was just looking for gifts," says MISAKA says MISAKA mounting an argument.
ミサカは お土産を
見てただけなんだからって―
ミサカはミサカは抗議してみる
Misaka?
ミサカ？
Hello? Is that you, Stiyl?
もしもし　ステイルか？
I've finished treating the girl.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）女学生の手当てが終わった
（上条）姫神は？
How is she?
I hope I never have to use that spell again.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
もう あんな術式は
二度と使いたくないね
In any case, it looks like she's gotten over the shock.
とりあえず
ショック症状からは脱したみたいだ
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
まあ あとは医者の仕事だが
The rest is up to the doctors.
お前…
You—
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
ああ？　何だ そのふぬけた声は
What's with that slacked voice? I'm not here to chit-chat with you—
僕は君となれ合うつもりは…
ウワッ！
I haven't had a chance to thank you yet.
（小萌(こもえ)）
先生は まだ“ありがとう”って
言ってないのです
If you hadn't been here, Himegami-chan would've...
もし あなたがいなかったら
姫神ちゃんは… 姫神ちゃんは…
Himegami-chan would've...
Stop it. We don't know whether she's going to be okay or not yet.
よせ　まだ
確実に助かると決まったわけでは…
But I... I...
（小萌）
それでも先生は… 先生は…
なんだか取り込み中のようだから
あとでな
You guys seem busy, so I'll call again later.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）土御門に電話しろ
（上条）うん？
Call Tsuchimikado!
Apparently he figured out something.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
何か つかんだらしい
ンッ… こちらも―
I'll catch up with you after I get rid of this.
この人を引き剥がしてから
ヤツのもとに向かう
Looks like I was right.
（土御門）
やっぱり当たりだったみたいだぜ
But how do we explain this hole in our theory?
だとすると あの矛盾は
どうなっちまうんだろうにゃ
（小萌）
あっ 吹寄(ふきよせ)ちゃん
Fukiyose-chan! How are you doing?
お体のほうは大丈夫なのですか？
（吹寄）
こっちは大丈夫です
I'm fine. Is the Daihaseisai proceeding as planned?
それより 大覇星祭のほうは
問題ありませんか？
（小萌）
それが
姫神ちゃんが大ピンチだったのです
Actually, Himegami-chan ran into a bit of trouble.
えっ？
まさか あのバカたちが また何か…
Did those idiots do something again?
She was assaulted by someone and taken to the hospital.
実は 何者かに襲われて
病院に運ばれたのです
襲われた？
Assaulted?!
If Kamijou-chan and his friends hadn't been there, things would have been really bad.
あそこに
上条ちゃんたちがいなかったら
大変なことになっていたかも
しれなかったのです
あっ… 今 神父さんが
Oh, that's the priest.
Mr. Priest!
神父さーん！
えっ？　神父さん？
Mr. Priest?
What on Earth is happening in this city?
（吹寄）
一体 この街で何が起こってるの？
I see...
（上条）
そうか　なら やっぱり
星座に発動のカギがあるってことか
So the key to activating it is in the constellations.
（土御門）
けどにゃ
However, as far as we know, it was last activated during the summer.
かつて使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)が使われたときは
夏だった
I don't think the autumn constellations will work quite so well.
秋の星座で代用できるとは
思えないぜ
We're still missing something.
まだ何かあるんだ
A gimmick that we haven't thought of.
俺たちの解いてない
ギミックってやつが
But we don't have time to sit around and ponder it.
けど
あれこれ考えてる時間もねえだろう
あっ イギリス清教
The Church of England?
Is this Stiyl Magnus-san?
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
そちらはステイル＝マグナスさんの
携帯電話でよろしいでしょうか？
You've got the wrong number!
（２人）
間違い電話かよ！
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
申し訳ありませんでした！
I'm very sorry!
ありゃ？　その声…
Wait, that voice...
Is that you, Orsola?
（上条）
オルソラか？
Oh my, thank you for your help last time.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
まあまあ あなたさまは…
先日はお世話になりました
Thanks to you, I've become very well-acquainted with—
おかげさまで こちらにも
すっかり慣れることができ…
（土御門）
いや 報告があるなら
早く伝えてくれないかにゃ？
Do you have any information to give us?
ええ　先日も神裂さんに―
Yes. Kanzaki-san showed me this delicious Japanese restaurant the other day—
おいしい日本料理店の場所を
紹介していただいて…
（上条）
だから とっとと つかんだ情報を
教えてくれってば！
We're asking you to report information you gathered!
Yes. I learned something in regards to the Croce di Pietro's activation conditions.
はい　使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)の使用条件について
分かりましたのでございます
It's a large-scale artifact that utilizes constellations.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
あれは 星座の力を
利用する大規模霊装なのだとか
We already managed to figure that much out.
悪い　それは もう分かってるんだ
I see...
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
そうでございますか
So you must already know that the conditions to activate it are always present, regardless of the time of year.
それでは 季節に関係なく
世界全土で自由に発動できることも
つかんでおいでだったので
ございますね
When Sherry-san and I found it, we were very excited.
シェリーさんと一緒に
見つけたときには―
やったと思いましたのに
（上条）
ちょっと待て　そりゃ 何の話だ？
Wait, what do you mean by that?
The Croce di Pietro can only be activated once the user had learned the characteristics of the area,
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)を使うためには―
使用するエリアの特性を
詳しく把握し―
and chooses one out of the 88 constellations which best corresponds to the chosen area.
そのエリアに最適な星座を
88の中から選択することで―
初めて
発動条件が整うのでございますよ
That means...
てことは…
Yes. There are many limitations, but theoretically, the Roman Church can use it to take over any part of the world.
はい
さまざまな制約はございますが
事実上 世界中のどこであっても
ローマ正教による支配が
可能となるのでございます
（上条）なっ…
（土御門）分かってきたぜ
I'm starting to get it.
It means Peter gave some leeway as to the region he affected with his teachings.
ペテロは自分の殉教の地に
幅を持たせてたってことだにゃ
She may be able to freely choose the location, but what about the date?
でも
場所は選べたとしても 日付は…
Peter-sama was executed on June 29th.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
ペテロさまが処刑されたのは
６月29日
That is the day the Croce di Pietro can be used at the Vatican.
ちょうど バチカンで使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)が
使える日付でございますね
So he deliberately got caught on that day? Prepared to die?
わざわざ その日に合わせて
捕まったってのか？
殺される覚悟を決めて
It's not that far-fetched.
ありえない話じゃないにゃ
…で オルソラ
今日 ９月19日に―
Orsola. Do you know where in Japan the Croce di Pietro can be used today, September 19th?
日本で使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)を使うための
ポイントってのも―
もう分かってんのか？
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）はい
Yes. But of course.
もちろんなので
ございますよ
（美鈴(みすず)）
あっ！　見て見て 美琴(みこと)ちゃん
Look at this, Mikoto-chan!
It's a pseudo-five-dimensional kaleidoscope!
（美琴）
疑似五次元万華鏡ですって
へえ 面白い！
How interesting!
Don't pick something so sketchy.
（美琴）
そんな
うさんくさい物(もん)に手を出さない
Get something that's more memorable.
もっと
思い出に浸れる物にしなさいよ
もう 乙女チックなんだから
You're such a girl.
はぁ？　だ… 黙れ バカ！
Shut up, Mother!
ハッ…
こ… このねっとりした視線は…
This slimy gaze...
（黒子(くろこ)）
そ… そのお方は
お姉様のご家族ですの？
I see. So, that person there is a member of your family.
まあ！　何ですの？
What is this? She's like a bigger version which still maintains that air of "Onee-sama."
このお姉様オーラの大インフレは…
ち… ちくしょう
こうなったら私も覚悟を決めますわ
Damn it. Now I must go all the way.
Bring it on!
まとめて かかってこいですのよ！
グフフッ…
ちょっと… 黒子 あんた…
Kuroko, are you seriously...
美琴ちゃんの“乙女チック”って
そういう方向だったの？
Mikoto-chan, don't tell me you're that  kind of girl?
（美琴）
えっ？　ち… 違うわよ！
No way!
ほら 黒子！
早く現実に戻ってきなさいってば！
Kuroko, snap back to reality!
もう！　目を覚ませ この…
おはよう！　おはよう！
Onee-sama...
Wake up! Good morning! Good morning!
Oh, it's that boy...
あら　あの子…
So, Oriana was walking around to check out all the important points?
じゃ オリアナが歩き回ってたのは
ポイントが使い物になるかどうか
確かめてたってわけか
ああ　これまでのは どこも
ビルや街路樹で空が隠されていた
Yeah. The sky was hidden from view in the places she visited, though.
残るポイントは１つ
きっと ここに来るはずにゃ
There's one last place. We should find her there.
（上条）
23学区の実験空港？
The 23rd District's Experimental Airport?
（土御門）
ここなら 空を隠す物は何もないぜ
There'll be nothing to hide the sky there.
Sorry for being late.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
遅くなったね
まったく… 何なんだ？　あの人は
Seriously, what is with that person?
人払いを使っても―
Even when I erase my presence, she notices me as soon as I leave the area of effect.
効果範囲から出る度に
捕捉し直してくるなんて…
What are we going to do now?
それより どうするんだ？
第23学区っていったら
ものすごい警備体制なんだろう？
The 23rd District has some crazy security.
Can we even get in?
俺たちが潜り込めるのか？
フッ… それは あれだ
Don't worry. This time around we can use the special permission I have.
俺だけにある今回かぎりの
特権ってやつを―
使っちまえばいいんだぜ
（上条）特権？
（土御門）フフッ…
Special permission?
Strange...
おかしいわね
It's time for the final preparations.
そろそろ仕上げの準備よ
（ﾘﾄﾞｳﾞｨｱ）
定刻には まだ時間があるのでは？
Isn't there more time before we can start?
The security here is fluctuating irregularly.
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）
警備状況が不自然に変動してる
It seems they've noticed my presence.
この近くにいることが
つかまれてるみたいね
Then, Belvedere's position is...
（ﾘﾄﾞｳﾞｨｱ）
ならば 天文台(ベルヴェデーレ)の位置も…
フフッ… 多分ね
Probably. But this is the best place to do it.
けど
いちばん使えそうな場所は ここよ
ここなら これ以上 一般人を
巻き込むこともないでしょうし
We can act freely here without involving civilians.
Then...
（ﾘﾄﾞｳﾞｨｱ）それでは…
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）ええ　そちらも準備して
Yes. Prepare yourself.
Let's drop Academy City right here.
ここで落としてしまいましょう
学園都市を
Like kicking a naive maiden of the light into the mud.
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）
今まで何も知らなかった光の乙女を
泥の中に突き飛ばすようにね
（土御門）
第23学区の警備状況を
少し変えてもらった
I had them change the 23rd District's security a bit.
We're going to use the confusion to our advantage.
この混乱の隙を突くぜ
The Croce di Pietro will activate immediately after sunset, most likely between 6 and 7.
使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)の発動は日没直後
恐らく 午後６時から７時の間
It will take 10 minutes to get to the 23rd District's terminal station.
23学区のターミナル駅まで10分
From there on, we will have 25 minutes to complete our mission.
到着してから リミットまで
25分しかないってことになる
Allow me to ask you one last thing. Do you intend to stand against Oriana as you are now?
一応 確認しておくが
その体で
オリアナの前に立つつもりかい？
フフッ… 休みてえのは
やまやまなんだがにゃ
I'd love to sit this one out, but I'm not sure you two can make it past the security detail on your own.
お前らだけで突破できるほど―
第23学区の警備は
甘くねえんですたい
そうかい
I see.
Once we step onto this train, there's no turning back.
この列車に乗ったら
もう後戻りはできない
From here on, there will be nothing but death.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
待っているのは殺し合いだけだ
Are you prepared, Kamijou Touma?
覚悟は決まったか？　上条当麻
Yeah. We need to bring an end to this.
ああ
ここで全部 終わりにするんだ
Also...
（上条）それから…
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）何だ？
What is it?
I don't intend to end it all here.
覚えておけ
俺は 殺し合いで
終わらせるつもりなんてねえよ
Touma isn't around?
（刀夜(とうや)）
当麻がいない？
（小萌）
え… えっと…
What do you mean?
（詩菜(しいな)）あの… それは どういう…
（小萌）申し訳ありません
I'm so sorry. I lost track of him despite being responsible for him.
大切なお子さまを
お預かりしている身でありながら
その動向がつかめないなんて…
（刀夜）
フゥ…
I just want to ask one thing.
ひとつだけ尋ねたいのですが
はい　何でしょう？
Of course. What is it?
当麻は
自発的に行動してるんですよね？
Touma is acting on his own will, right?
誰かに
引っ張り回されているのではなく
He's not being dragged around by someone?
あっ… はい　そうなのですよ
Yes, it's exactly as you say.
フフッ… なら 当麻にとって―
Then whatever he's doing now must be more important to him than the competition.
競技以上の
価値ある行いというわけだ
I can't think of a reason to stop him.
（刀夜）
止める理由は思い浮かばないかな
Yes.
（詩菜）
はい
May the sky and the heavens become a great roof to protect those within.
（ﾘﾄﾞｳﾞｨｱ）
天の空を屋根に変え
この地に安住を築くために―
May the saints and angels bless this place.
いざ 聖十二使徒のご加護を
The basic principle of the security here is the utilization of the sky.
ここの警備の基本は空だ
何せ 隠れる場所なんて
ほとんどないからにゃ
There's almost nowhere to hide, after all.
Then, how did Oriana manage to get in?
じゃ
オリアナは どうやって空港に？
She must have made prior preparations.
とっくに
どうにかしてるはずだにゃ
土御門　僕たちは時間が惜しい
Tsuchimikado. We're short on time.
にゃ～！　あれを使うんだよ
I'm aware. We're going to be using that.
There's a regular airport nearby, so this airspace is crowed with airliners and such.
（土御門）
ここは一般の空港も近い
旅客機や実験機などで
空は混雑してるんだにゃ
In order to avoid a collision, the surveillance planes change their routes periodically.
空中衝突を避けるために―
監視用の機体の巡回ルートが
そこそこ変わるんだぜ
We can use the blind spot that this creates to slip through unnoticed.
死角に潜り込めば
多分 なんとかなるはずにゃ
（上条）ハッ… 待て 土御門！
（土御門）何だ？　カミやん
Tsuchimikado, stop!
What's wrong, Kami-yan?
Tsuchimikado!
（上条）
土御門！　大丈夫か 土御門
Are you all right?
Go, Kami-yan.
（土御門）
行け　カミやん
You have to destroy that page and continue on.
そのページを破壊して ２人で行け
What about you?
お前は どうするんだよ？
Stiyl, can't you do something with your magic?
ステイル
お前の魔術で治せないのか？
ンッ… あちらが それを待つものか
Do you really think she'll wait for us?
Kamijou Touma!
上条当麻！
Fire is in my hand.
この手に炎を
Thy shape is a sword; and thy purpose is to cut!
その形は剣(つるぎ)　その役は断罪！
Hurry!
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）急げ！
（上条）ンッ…
フフッ…
あの聖人は やっぱり来ないのね
Looks like that saint really isn't going to show. That makes only three of you.
…となると
そちらは３人だけってことかしら
The field that she just erected will cut all communication.
結界か　あらゆる通信を切断したな
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）アアッ！
（上条）ステイル！
Stiyl!
My, my. I’m not so sensitive that I can be satisfied with one hand.
あら まあ！
片手間で満足させられるほど
おねえさんは感じやすくはないわよ
Shatter!
砕けろ！
As always, your hips run out of gas way too quickly.
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）
相変わらず腰が砕けるのが早いわね
お前は ここで止める
使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)も使わせない
Your ride ends here. I won't allow you to use the Croce di Pietro.
（上条）
お前が
学園都市をメチャクチャにして
You think you can just mess with Academy City and disrupt the Daihaseisai like that?
大覇星祭を台なしにするってんなら
必ず ここで止めてやる！
It all ends now!
フフッ…
メチャメチャってのは ひどいわね
Disrupt? That's a little mean.
The Croci di Pietro might break the walls between science and magic, leading the world to happiness.
使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)は
魔術と科学の壁を取り去る
世界中の人々を
幸せに導くかもしれないのよ
Happiness?
（上条）
幸せ？　いいな それ
Sounds nice, doesn't it?
I know that it’s a good word.
なんとなく
それが いい言葉だってのは分かる
But my problem is that using the Croce di Pietro will ruin the Daihaseisai.
けどな 俺にとって 困るのは―
てめえが
今ここで使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)を使って―
大覇星祭を
つぶしちまうことなんだよ
You don't know how many people were looking forward to the Daihaseisai.
（上条）
どれだけの人間が
大覇星祭を大切に思っているか
どんなご立派な宗教で
身を固めたところで―
Regardless of your religious beliefs, you have no right to ruin their fun!
その思いを奪う権利なんて
てめえにあるはずがねえだろうが！
You think that kind of emotionally charged speech will reach me?
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）
その程度の感情論で
おねえさんが揺らぐと思ってるの？
If there was any risk of people getting hurt, I wouldn't have done this in the first place.
それくらいで傷つくようなら
最初から動いてないわよ
今のセリフ てめえが傷つけた
吹寄と姫神の前でも言えるのか？
Could you say that in front of Fukiyose and Himegami, the two that you hurt?
That's all I wanted to say to you.
結局 俺が言いたいのは それだけだ
だが まだ
この街で何かやるっていうなら
If you still have even a single thought of harming this city in any way,
その幻想を
カケラも残さず ぶち殺してやる！
～♪
then I'll have to crush that ridiculous illusion of yours!
Next Episode
Even if you have an objective.
（上条）
いくら目的があったって―
Even if you have a glorious ideal.
いくら
すばらしい理想があったって
I won't allow it.
決して
お前たちの勝手にはさせない
絶対に終わりにはしない！
I'll smash you to pieces!
Next time: "Croce di Pietro."
次回 「使徒十字(クローチェディピエトロ)」
When science and magic cross paths, this epic will begin!
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる